const data = {
  react: [
    {
      question: "Which is the most popular JavaScript framework?",
      options: ["Angular", "React", "Svelte", "Vue"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Which company invented React?",
      options: ["Google", "Apple", "Netflix", "Facebook"],
      correctOption: 3,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "What's the fundamental building block of React apps?",
      options: ["Components", "Blocks", "Elements", "Effects"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "What's the name of the syntax we use to describe the UI in React components?",
      options: ["FBJ", "Babel", "JSX", "ES2015"],
      correctOption: 2,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "How to pass data into a child component?",
      options: ["State", "Props", "PropTypes", "Parameters"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },

    {
      question:
        "Which hook to use for an API request on the component's initial render?",
      options: ["useState", "useEffect", "useRef", "useReducer"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
  html: [
    {
      question: "The <p> tap is used for: ",
      options: ["Paragraph", "page", "Pointer", "Parser"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Waht is the output of this code ? <div class='sum'>(3+6)/2</div>",
      options: ["4", "(3+6)/2", "4.5", "6"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "HTML elements are divided into two categories: block level and inline elements.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The navigation menu of a webpage can only be placed in the <nav> tag.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "To make the table have the whole width of the viewer's browser window irrespective of its width, you should specify a table width of:",
      options: ["50%", "1000px", "100%", "600px"],
      correctOption: 2,
      points: 10,
    },

    {
      question:
        "When using the <script> tap, we can either use the 'src' attribute to link of write the Javascript inside the element.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
  javaScript: [
    {
      question: "Javascript is used for: ",
      options: ["Paragraph", "page", "Pointer", "Parser"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Waht is the output of this code ? <div class='sum'>(3+6)/2</div>",
      options: ["4", "(3+6)/2", "4.5", "6"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "HTML elements are divided into two categories: block level and inline elements.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The navigation menu of a webpage can only be placed in the <nav> tag.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "To make the table have the whole width of the viewer's browser window irrespective of its width, you should specify a table width of:",
      options: ["50%", "1000px", "100%", "600px"],
      correctOption: 2,
      points: 10,
    },

    {
      question:
        "When using the <script> tap, we can either use the 'src' attribute to link of write the Javascript inside the element.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
  python: [
    {
      question: "Python tap is used for: ",
      options: ["Paragraph", "page", "Pointer", "Parser"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "Waht is the output of this code ? <div class='sum'>(3+6)/2</div>",
      options: ["4", "(3+6)/2", "4.5", "6"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "HTML elements are divided into two categories: block level and inline elements.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "The navigation menu of a webpage can only be placed in the <nav> tag.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 1,
      points: 10,
    },
    {
      question:
        "To make the table have the whole width of the viewer's browser window irrespective of its width, you should specify a table width of:",
      options: ["50%", "1000px", "100%", "600px"],
      correctOption: 2,
      points: 10,
    },

    {
      question:
        "When using the <script> tap, we can either use the 'src' attribute to link of write the Javascript inside the element.",
      options: ["True", "False"],
      correctOption: 0,
      points: 10,
    },
  ],
};
export default data;
